A Guide to the Records of the Governor's Fellows Program, Secretary of the Commonwealth, 2014-2019
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Governor's Fellows Program, Secretary of the Commonwealth, 2014-2019
The Library of Virginia
53507
3.05 cu. ft. (9 boxes)
Virginia. Secretary of the Commonwealth
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per code of Virginia 42.1-78. It may be necessary for an archivist to review records in this collection before they are served to patrons for research purposes in order to redact or remove privacy protected or confidential information. Restricted information includes forms with birthdates and school transcripts.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 14 January 2022 by Office of the Governor, 1111 E. Broad St., Richmond, Virginia, 23219.
Biographical Information
The Governor's Fellows program aimed to provide high quality applied learning opportunities to students from the Commonwealth currently enrolled in undergraduate and graduate programs. Governor Charles S. Robb appointed A. E. Dick Howard as counselor to the Governor in 1982. One of his actions was to create the Governor's Fellows Program, a program that invited college and graduate students to apply to serve for a summer in the Governor's Office. Through professional mentorships, community service, and challenging projects, the mission was to strengthen ties of the office to Virginia communities.
Scope and Content
Records, 2014-2019, of the Governor's Fellows Program, under the direction of the Secretary of the Commonwealth. Included are applications, correspondence, letters of recommendation, and college transcripts of applicants for the program. The records cover the administrations of Governor Terry McAuliffe (2014-2018) and Governor Ralph Northam (2018-2022).
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically and then alphabetically within each year.
Contents List
- A-B, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- C, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- D-H, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- I-K, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- L-M, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- N-P, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Q-Z, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- B, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Ca-Ce, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Ch-Co, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- D, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- F, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ga-Go, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Go-Gy, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Ha-Hi, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hi-Ho, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- J-K, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- La-Li, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lo-Ly, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Mc, Ma-Me, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Mi-Mu, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- N-Q, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- R, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- S, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- T, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- W-Z, 2016 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- A, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- B, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- C, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- D-E, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- F-G, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- H-J, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- K-L, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- M, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- N-P, 2017 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- R-S, 2017 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- T-Y, 2017 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- A, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- B, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Ca-Ch, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Cl-Cu, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- D-E, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- F, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- G, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- H-J, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- K, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- L, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Mc, Ma-Me, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Mi-N, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- O-P, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- R, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Sa-Si, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Sm-Sw, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- T, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- V, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- W, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Z, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- A-C, 2019 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- D-E, 2019 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- F-G, 2019 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- H-K, 2019 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- L-P, 2019 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- R-S, 2019 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- W-Z, 2019 (Box 9, Folder 3)